https://childrensmiraclenetworkhospitals.org/privacy-policy/

Sign In
Forgot?
Why Have a CMN Hospital Account?
Create a fundraiser.
Manage your recurring donations.
Keep up to date with your local CMN Hospital.
Create an account
Search our library
Quick Links
CMN Hospitals NationalPrivacy PolicyFinancialsCareersNewsroomContact
Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals
Privacy Policy
Last Updated: June 25th, 2019
What this Privacy Policy Does and Does Not Cover
This Privacy Policy covers how Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals (“Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals,” “we,” or “us”) treats personal information that we collect and receive through the Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals websites at http://www.childrensmiraclenetworkhospitals.org/ and www.mymiracleband.org and our “Give Miracles” mobile application (the “Services”). In this Privacy Policy, “personal information” means information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
This Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of local children’s hospitals, companies that Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals does not own or control, or to people that Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals collects personal information when you donate directly to Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals. If you donate directly to a hospital, then we may receive your personal information to the extent that the hospital shares it with us in accordance with its own privacy policy.
When you donate, we ask for information such as your name, email address, and zip code. Once you donate to Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals, you are not anonymous to us.
When you use the Services, we may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address and the page you request, through automated means such as cookies. A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. Most browsers will tell you how to stop accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, and how to disable existing cookies. Please note, however, that without cookies you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the features of the Services. To the extent the information we automatically collect through the Services consists of, or is paired with, your personal information, we will treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
We may also use third-party analytics tools such as Google Analytics that collect information about use of the Services and user traffic). Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals uses information for the following general purposes: to improve our services, collect donations, contact you, conduct research, enforce our agreements, comply with applicable legal requirements and industry standards, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
We may disclose aggregated information about our donors, and information that does not identify any individual donor, without restriction.
Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals will share your donor contact information with the Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals participating hospital selected during the donor’s gift designation. The donor is advised to review the receiving institution’s privacy policy to see how they will use their donor information.
Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
We disclose information to contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our services and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them;
We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
If we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Children’s Miracle Network Hospital’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law; and
We will transfer information about you to a buyer or other transferee in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, sale, or other transfer of some or all of our assets. In this event, Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
Correction/Updating Personal Information
You can change your donor information (name, address, etc.) in our database by contacting our customer support team at 801-214-7400, or by clicking here. You may also reach out to our customer support team to request the deletion of your personal information, although we may not accommodate a request to change or delete information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect. If you have received a promotional email from us, you can also opt out of receiving future promotional emails from us by following the unsubscribe instructions contained in such email.
Donors who have previously opted-in to external communication lists and services can also use the above contacts to inform Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals that you no longer wish to have your personal information shared in this manner.
Confidentiality, Security, and Retention
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. In certain areas Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals uses industry-standard TLS-encryption to protect data transmissions
Do Not Track
Your web browser may let you choose your preference as to whether you want to allow the collection of information about your online activities over time and across different websites or online services. At this time, the Services do not respond to the preferences you may have set in your web browser regarding such collection of your information, and the we may continue to collect information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.
Children’s Personal Information
The Services are not directed to, and Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from, children under the age of 13. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please contact us as set forth below.
Data Transfers
Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals is based in the State of Utah in the United States. When we obtain information about you, we may transfer, process, and store such information outside of the country in which you reside, including in the United States. By using the Services or by donating to us, you consent to the transfer to and processing and storage of your information in countries outside of your country of residence, which may have different data protection laws than those in the country where you reside.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals may update this Privacy Policy in its sole discretion. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. The date this Privacy policy was last updated is at the top of this page. We encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically to check for any updates.
Contact Us
If you have questions or suggestions, please send them to us by clicking here.
CMN Hospitals NationalPrivacy PolicyFinancialsCareersNewsroomContact
205 West 700 South Salt Lake City, UT 84101
© 2020 Children’s Miracle Network Hospitals, a not-for-profit, section 501(c)(3)
